Guide to the George A. Lindbeck Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Conferences/Lectures, 1942-2006, n.d.; Series VI
  - Original files
    - "J. J. Thiessen Lectures: The Church as Hermeneutical Community: Jews, Christians, and the Bible", Canadian Mennonite Bible College, Winnipeg, MB, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 568)
    - Annual Spring Banquet: Center for Catholic and Evangelical Theology, Northfield, MN, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 569)
    - "International Theology Conference: A New Testament Model for Dealing with Pluralism", Shalom Hartman Institute, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 570)
    - "4th Sunday Advent" (Box 28, Folder 571)
    - "7th After Trinity", nd (Box 28, Folder 572)
    - "8th Sunday Trinity" (Box 28, Folder 573)
    - "Bondage and Freedom in Ethics and Politics, IV" (Box 28, Folder 574)
    - "Christ Alone Adequate for Post-War Reconstruction", nd (Box 28, Folder 575)
    - "Doubt Confusion", nd (Box 28, Folder 577)
    - "Easter", nd (Box 28, Folder 578)
    - "The Evangelical Possibilities of Roman Catholic Theology", nd (Box 29, Folder 579)
    - "From Reform to Separation (1530-1580)", nd (Box 29, Folder 580)
    - Gonzaga Lectures, St. Michael's, nd (Box 29, Folder 581)
    - "Institute I", nd (Box 29, Folder 582)
    - "Korea", nd (Box 29, Folder 583)
    - "The Limits of the Development and Reformulation of Doctrine" (Box 29, Folder 584)
    - "Liturgical Revival III", nd (Box 29, Folder 585)
    - "Liturgy", Chicago Catholic Biblical Institute (unused), nd (Box 29, Folder 586)
    - "Lutheran-Catholic Dialogue: IV and V, Lutheran Presentation", Washington D.C. (Box 29, Folder 587)
    - "Needs and Difficulties, IV" (Box 29, Folder 588)
    - "Protestant View of Ecumenism", Hartford, nd (Box 29, Folder 589)
    - "Roman Catholic", New York, nd (Box 29, Folder 590)
    - "Roman Catholic", nd (Box 29, Folder 591)
    - "Roman Catholic VI", nd (Box 29, Folder 592)
    - "Roman Catholic Theologians" (incomplete), nd (Box 29, Folder 593)
    - "Roman Catholic V, Salvation", nd (Box 29, Folder 594)
    - "The Sectarian Future of the Church", Woodstock Theological College, New York, nd (Box 29, Folder 595)
    - "Theology of Mystical Body, lecture IV", nd (Box 29, Folder 596)
    - Three Lectures on the Augsburg Confession, nd (Box 29, Folder 597)
    - Vacation Bible School, Yakima, nd (Box 29, Folder 598)
    - "Vatican Council", nd (Box 29, Folder 599)
    - "Why Think About Death?", nd (Box 29, Folder 600)
    - Yale Chaplains, nd (Box 29, Folder 601)
    - Miscellaneous, nd (Box 29, Folder 602)
    - Miscellaneous, nd (Box 29, Folder 603)
    - "Church Speech", East Orange, nd (Box 28, Folder 576)
  - Addendum
    - Untitled sermon - "Proposed Chapel", 1952 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - "Expectations for Coming Vatican Council" - speech in South America, 1962 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - "The Roman Catholic Contribution to Ecumenism" - YDS opening convocation, 1964 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - "Vatican II and the Dialogue" - Yale Alumni Seminar, 1965 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - "On Observing Ecumenical Councils" - Talk at LCA district; Chapel talk; "Current Protestant Thinking about the Ecumenical Movement" - National Worship on Christian Unity, Boston, 1965 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - "Christian Faith and the Ideal of the Magnanimous Man": Hollins College, 1965 (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - Theological Consultation between Representatives of the Bishops' Commission for Ecumenical Affairs and the USA National Committee of the Lutheran World Federation (Chicago), 1966 (Box 76, Folder 181)
    - Untitled talks, 1966, 1967 (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Seminar on "The Role of the Law in the Church", late 1960s (Box 76, Folder 182)
    - Villanova University Conference, 1969 (Box 76, Folder 183)
    - "The Official Dialogue - Does It Make a Difference?" - Boston LCA ministers, 1971 (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - "Religion and the Crisis in Values" - Conference on the Formation and Transmission of Values in Society, Collegeville, MN, 1972, 1973 (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - "Papacy and Ius Divinum: A Lutheran View" - New Orleans meeting, U.S. Catholic-Lutheran Dialogue, 1972 (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - "Infallibility" - Pere Marquette Lecture in Theology, Marquette University, 1972 (Box 88, Folder 12)
    - "The Present and Future of Prayer or Catholicity and Immediacy: Reflections on the Ecumenical Problem of Religious Experience", 1972 (Box 88, Folder 13)
    - "The Dynamics of Ecumenism"- The Catholic Theological Society of America, 1973 (Box 88, Folder 14)
    - "Religion and the Crisis of Values: Prospects for New Sects and Old Churches" - Lawrence University, Appleton, WI, 1973 (Box 88, Folder 15)
    - "Traditional Christian Attitudes Towards Jews", 1973 (Box 88, Folder 16)
    - "Lutherans and Catholics in Dialogue: IV and V: A Lutheran Presentation - Washington, D.C., 1975 (Box 88, Folder 18)
    - "Scientific and Theological Revolutions: the Uses and Misuses of T. S. Kuhn" - Cambridge, 1976 (Box 88, Folder 19)
    - Presentation for panel on Martin Buber, 1976 (Box 88, Folder 20)
    - Handwritten notes for presentations on Lutheran - Roman Catholic relations, 1977 (Box 88, Folder 21)
    - "Religion in the USSR" - for Silliman College Fellows "Papacy and the Modern World" - for Ezra Stiles College Fellows, 1978 (Box 88, Folder 22)
    - Untitled talk - Riverside Church "On Redemptor Hominis" and "Hesychastic Prayer and the Christianizing of Platonism" - Tantur Ecumenical Institute, 1979 (Box 88, Folder 23)
    - Die Grenzen der Verschiedenheit im Verstandnis von Rechtfertigung: ein Versuch aus noramerikanisher Sicht - Munich, 1980 (Box 88, Folder 25)
    - Response to Cardinal Willebrands at program on ecumenism- Assumption College, 1980 (Box 88, Folder 26)
    - "Summary of the Argument" (re. university divinity schools), 1980 (Box 88, Folder 27)
    - Response to Rosemary Ruether - Chicago Sermon at Bethesda Lutheran Church - New Haven, 1984 (Box 88, Folder 28)
    - "Comment on 'Jonathan Edwards' Christology" by Robert W. Jenson" - Princeton, ATS meeting, 1984 (Box 88, Folder 29)
    - IJCIC-WCC Consultation (Harvard University), 1984 (Box 76, Folder 184)
    - New Haven Theology Discussion Group, 1985 (Box 76, Folder 185)
    - "The Reformation Heritage and Christian Unity" - Union Theological Seminary, Richmond, 1985 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - "Ecumenism, Ministry and the ELCA" - Holyoke, 1987 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - "The Church's Mission to a Postmodern Culture" - Trinity Institute, 1987 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Ordination sermon for Eric Wefeld Response to Gordon Kaufman on Hans Frei - Boston Remarks at AAR - Chicago, 1988 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Austin Presbyterian Seminary lectures, 1988 (Box 76, Folder 186)
    - Untitled talk - YDS faculty conference Untitled talk - XII Final Session, 1989 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - "Reformation" - YDS chapel, 1990 (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Sermon - Advent I - YDS chapel, 1991 (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - "The Structure of the Communio": Venice, September 23-28, 1991 (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Sermons, chapel talks, 1992 (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - Response to George Weigel, 1991 (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - Sermon - YDS chapel, 1993 (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - The Aquinas-Luther Conference (Lenoir-Rhyne College), 1993 (Box 76, Folder 187)
    - Lecture on "Atonement in Current Debate", 1994 (Box 76, Folder 188)
    - Notes for lecture at Princeton, 1994 (Box 89, Folder 17)
    - The New Testament and Ethics Conference (Duke University), 1995 (Box 76, Folder 189)
    - "Beginning or Ending? Commentary on Richard B. Hays' Community, Cross, New Creation: A New Testament Ethics - Duke University, 1995 (Box 89, Folder 18)
    - Wheaton Theology Conference (Wheaton College), 1995 (Box 76, Folder 190)
    - "One Gospel: The Gospel Claim to Uniqueness in the Context of Religious Pluralism": The National Conference of the Australian and New Zealand Association of Theological Studies and The Australian and New Zealand Society for Theological Studies (Australian National University), 1995 (Box 76, Folder 191)
    - Draft of address at Nanjing Theological Seminary, 1996 (Box 89, Folder 19)
    - "Concluding Scientific Theory of Why There Are No Holmerians (on the Occasion of Paul Holmer's Eightieth Year)" - St. Paul, MN, 1996 (Box 89, Folder 20)
    - Nature of Doctrine presentation at Macalester College, 1996 (Box 89, Folder 21)
    - Jesuit School of Theology at Berkeley commencement speech, 1997 (Box 76, Folder 192)
    - Burke Library lecture on Justification, 1997 (Box 76, Folder 193)
    - New Haven Theological Discussion Group, 1997 (Box 77, Folder 194)
    - Sermons at Bethesda Lutheran Church and Marquand Chapel, Yale Divinity School (inauguration of Luther Studies Program at YDS), 1997 (Box 89, Folder 22)
    - Forum on intercommunion lecture (Yale Divinity School), 1998 (Box 77, Folder 195)
    - Yale Interdisciplinary Millenialism Seminar (Yale University), 1998 (Box 77, Folder 196)
    - Day Associates Lecture, Yale Divinity School Library: "Robert Calhoun as Historian of Doctrine", 1998 (Box 77, Folder 197)
    - Lent IV Bible sermon (Bethesda), 1998 (Box 77, Folder 198)
    - Advent sermon - Immanuel, NYC, 1998 (Box 89, Folder 24)
    - "Rich Trees and Wild Branches" - response to Kepnw, Meskin, and Batnitzky - AJS, Boston, 1998 (Box 89, Folder 25)
    - "Religion & Scholarship: Present Positions. Future Prospects?" conference (Notre Dame University), 1999 (Box 77, Folder 199)
    - "The Yale Conference on Ecumenism: Justification and the Future of the Ecumenical Movement" (Yale Divinity School), 2000 (Box 77, Folder 200)
    - Response to the Paul Wattson Christian Unity Award (Graymoor Institute), 2000 (Box 77, Folder 201)
    - Response to Cardinal Cassidy (Notre Dame University), 2000 (Box 77, Folder 202)
    - Andover Newton Theological School lecture: "Dominus Iesus: A Lutheran Perspective", 2001 (Box 77, Folder 203)
    - Wycliffe College (Toronto) lecture: "The Church as Israel and the Ecumenism of the Future", 2001 (Box 77, Folder 204)
    - Princeton University lecture: "Community and Metanarrative", 2001 (Box 77, Folder 205)
    - "Faith and Order Conference in North America" (Notre Dame University), 2001 (Box 77, Folder 206)
    - Response to Gabriel Fackre - ATS, Princeton, 2001 (Box 89, Folder 23)
    - "Apocalypse and Violence: Historical and Contemporary Perspectives" conference (Yale University), 2002 (Box 77, Folder 207)
    - "God and the Ethics of Belief" conference (Yale University), 2002 (Box 77, Folder 208)
    - "Truth: Interdisciplinary Dialogues in a Pluralist Age" conference (Claremont School of Theology), 2002 (Box 77, Folder 209)
    - "Espoir et Liberté: Hommage á Klauspeter Blaser" colloquium (Universite de Lausanne), 2003 (Box 78, Folder 210)
    - "George A. Lindbeck et The Nature of Doctrine " colloquium (Universite de Lausanne), 2003 (Box 78, Folder 211)
    - "Interreligious Relations and Christian Ecumenism: Revisiting Chapter 3 of The Nature of Doctrine - Lausanne, 1993 (Box 89, Folder 27)
    - Miscellaneous materials from French colloquiums (Universite de Lausanne), 2003 (Box 78, Folder 212)
    - "What is Marriage: A Theological Conference on Human Sexuality and Christian Marriage" (St. Olaf College), 2005 (Box 78, Folder 213)
    - Oxford Studies in World Christianity workshop (Yale University), 2006 (Box 78, Folder 214)
    - "Church and World at Vatican II" (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - "Response to R. Huetter"; "Response to Bruce Marshall", n.d. (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - "Messiahship and Incarnation: Particularity and Universality are Reconciled" (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - "Lecture Two: Remaining Problems and the Ecumenical Context" (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - "Interpretation: the Christology of the Fathers" seminar series, Ecumenical Institute, Tantur, 1979 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - "Singapore Lectures" - Session VI: The Church, no date (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - "On Being Lutheran in an Ecumenical Age", no date (Box 92, Folder 7)
- Collected Materials: Theological Education, Series VII
  - Art History
    - "The Field of Art History and Theological Education" by J. Cook (Box 30, Folder 604)
  - Black Theology
    - "Black Power and Church Power" by R.E. Sykes, in Journal for the Scientific Study of Religion, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 605)
    - "Toward an Interim Assessment of Black Theology" by William Jones in Reflection, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 606)
    - "Proposal for Black Studies Program", 1974 (Box 30, Folder 607)
  - Church
    - "The Vocation of a Church in America: A Sociologist's View" by Guy E. Swanson in Christian Faith and Industrial Society, n.2, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 608)
    - "The Gathering Storm in the Churches" by Jeffrey K. Hadden, Doubleday Press, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 609)
    - "The Church Alive and Changing" by Joseph C. Hough, Jr. in Christian Century, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 610)
    - "The German Lutheran Church and the Rise of National Socialism" by Hans Tiefel in Church History, v.41 n.3, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 611)
    - "The Not So Open Church" by Michael Novak in Commonweal, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 612)
    - "'Strictness' and Church Membership" by Thomas R. McFaul in Christian Century, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 613)
    - "Ritual, Cult, Worship" by John T. Ford in Religious Studies Review, v. 12 n.2, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 614)
    - "Can the Non-Conservative Seminaries Help the Churches?" by Harrellson, nd (Box 30, Folder 615)
    - "The Church and Its Purpose" by H.R. Niebuhr in The Purpose of the Church and Its Ministry (Box 30, Folder 616)
    - "The Man Who Wants to Scrap Schools" by John Davy (Box 30, Folder 617)
    - "Theology and Prayer: Some Conceptual Reminders" by D.E. Saliers in Worship, v.48 n.4 (Box 30, Folder 618)
  - Culture
    - "Religion, Culture, and the New Student Activism" in Remembering the Answers, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 619)
    - "The Counterculture: It Just Won't Go Away" by Myron B. Bloy, Jr. in Commonweal, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 620)
    - "The Eros Ethos Cult in the Counterculture" by Richard King in Psychology Today, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 621)
    - "The Struggle for Cultural Rebirth" by Robert Jay Lifton in Harper's, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 622)
    - "The Unfound Generation in Religious Thought" by Martin E. Marty in Christian Century, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 623)
    - "Charting the New Religious Consciousness" by Martin E. Marty in Christian Century, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 624)
    - "Theology as Modus Operandi" by Gerhard O. Forde in Worship, v. 21, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 625)
    - "Dying He Lives: Biblical Image, Biblical Narrative and Redemptive Jesus" by Michael Root in Semeia, n.30, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 626)
    - "Christian Existence Today: Essays on Church, World, and Living Inbetween" by Stanley Hauerwas, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 627)
    - "Equality and the Fate of Theism in Modern Culture" by Gene Outka in Journal of Religion, v. 67 n.3, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 628)
    - "Atonement", nd (Box 30, Folder 629)
    - "Culture: The Pulse of Freedom: American Liberties 1920s-1970s" by R.D. Gastil, nd (Box 30, Folder 630)
    - "Image-Symbols and Event-Symbols" by J.V. Langmead Casserley in Cross Currents (Box 30, Folder 631)
    - "The Necessary Utopia" by John P. Sisk, nd (Box 30, Folder 632)
    - "The Problem", nd (Box 30, Folder 633)
    - "The Sectarian Temptation: Reflections on Theology, the Church and the University" by James M. Gustafson (Box 30, Folder 634)
  - Department of Theological Education
    - Reports, nd (Box 30, Folder 635)
  - Education
    - "From Purpose to Curriculum" by Louis H. Gunnemann in Theological Education, v.II n.3, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 636)
    - "The Renewal of the Training for the Priesthood" in Concilium, v.43, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 637)
    - "Some Issues in Theological Education" by Owen C. Thomas in Theological Education, v. V n.4, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 638)
    - "Theological Education as Professional Education" by James M. Gustafson in Theological Education, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 639)
    - "Letter to a Prospective Seminarian" by Wayne Grudem in Christianity Today, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 640)
    - "Theological Education" in Christian Century, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 641)
    - "On Finding the Unfound Generation: The Young Theologian in America" by Dennis M. Campbell in Christian Century, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 642)
    - "Readiness for Ministry Survey: What Do You Consider Most Important in a Beginning Minister?" in American Association of Theological Schools, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 643)
    - "Wie Hauptschuler die Bundesrepublik Erkennen Sollen" by Friedrick Karl Fromme in Frankfurter Allgemeine Zeitung, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 644)
    - "Convocation of Teaching Theologians of the ELCA: Summary Paper", 1990 (Box 30, Folder 645)
    - "Theological Education in Disarray" by H. Eberhard von Waldow (Box 30, Folder 646)
    - "Theological Education: Rich Man's Slave or Poor Man's Servant?" by Tom Boomershine in Katallagete, nd (Box 30, Folder 647)
  - Employment
    - "Functional Specialities in Theology" by Bernard J. F. Lonergan in Gregoriamem, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 648)
    - "Ecumenical Theology: Vocation or Profession?" by Paul S. Minear, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 649)
  - Ministry
    - "Dittes on the Ministry" by Leroy T. Howe in Reflection, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 650)
  - Religion
    - "The Fire We Can Light: The Role of Religion in a Suddenly Different World" by Martin E. Marty in Christian Century, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 651)
    - "Religion in the American Revolution" by Dean M. Kelley in Christianity and Crisis, v. 34 n. 10, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 652)
    - "Chapter Fifteen: New Forms of Religion in the Seminary" by Robert Wuthnow in On Conformity and Rebellion among Religious Professionals (Box 30, Folder 653)
  - Rockefeller Report
    - "The Training of American Rabbis" by Charles S. Liebman in American Jewish Yearbook, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 654)
    - "Preliminary Working Paper on University-Related Theological Education" by George Lindbeck, Karl Deutsch, and Nathan Glazer, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 655)
    - "Preliminary Working Paper on University-Related Theological Education" by George Lindbeck, Karl Deutsch, and Nathan Glazer, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 656)
    - "Fading Big Five" in Time, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 657)
    - "New Approach is Urged in Study of Theology" by Kenneth A. Briggs in New York Times, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 658)
    - "Non-Practicing Divinity Students" by Chris Kenrick in Christian Science Monitor, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 659)
    - "Theologian Finds Gap Between Independent Divinity Schools and Churches" by Henry Romney, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 660)
    - "'Time' Story Irks Yale Dean" by John Knoble in New Haven Register, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 661)
    - "University Divinity Schools: A Report on Ecclesiastically Independent Theological Education" by George Lindbeck, Karl Deutsch, and Nathan Glazer in Working Papers: The Rockefeller Foundation, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 662)
    - "University Divinity Schools: A Report on Ecclesiastically Independent Theological Education" by George Lindbeck, Karl Deutsch, and Nathan Glazer in Working Papers: The Rockefeller Foundation, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 663)
    - "Working Paper on Aspects of University-Related Theological Education" by George Lindbeck, Karl Deutsch, and Nathan Glazer, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 664)
    - "Working Paper on Aspects of University-Related Theological Education" by George Lindbeck, Karl Deutsch, and Nathan Glazer, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 665)
    - Consultation Notes, nd (Box 31, Folder 666)
    - Data, nd (Box 31, Folder 667)
    - Deans' Responses (incl. University of Chicago), nd (Box 31, Folder 668)
    - "University of Chicago Response to 'Working Paper on Aspects of University Related Theological Education", nd (Box 31, Folder 669)
    - "University of Chicago Response to 'Working Paper on Aspects of University-Related Theological Eduvation'", nd (Box 31, Folder 670)
  - Seven Schools
    - "Defining the Issues" by Michael Novak at Conference on the Future of Theology, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 671)
    - "Memorandum on Theological Education for the Rockefeller-Seven Deans Meeting" by George Lindbeck, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 672)
    - "Memorandum on Theological Education for Rockefeller-Seven Deans Meeting" by Henri J. M. Nouwen, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 673)
    - "Reflections of Theological Education for Meeting of Seven Theological School with Rockefeller Foundation" by David Burrell, University of Notre Dame, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 674)
    - "Some Objectives of Theological Education" by J. Brooke Mosley, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 675)
    - "Perspectives for Talking with Lindbeck" in American Association of Theological Schools, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 676)
    - "Sunday Morning Session" (Box 31, Folder 677)
    - "To the Deans of the Seven Seminaries and their Consultants" by A.C. McGill, Harvard Divinity School (Box 31, Folder 678)
  - Social Science
    - "The Sociology of Knowledge and the Sociology of Religion in the Catholic University" by Andrew M. Greeley in Cross Currents, v. XIX, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 679)
    - "Faith, Utility, and the Legitimacy of Science" by Edward Shils (Box 31, Folder 680)
    - "On the Nature and Condition of Social Science" by Marc J. Roberts (Box 31, Folder 681)
    - "Religion im Umbruch" by Jakobus Wossner in Bucher, nd (Box 31, Folder 682)
  - Society for Theological Discussion
    - "Pari Pistatis Affectu: Scripture and Tradition at the Council of Trent" by Jaroslav Pelikan, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 683)
  - Taize
    - "Lettre de Taize", 1977 (Box 31, Folder 684)
    - "La Communaute Oecumenque de Taize", nd (Box 31, Folder 685)
  - Theology
    - "The Situation of Theology in Theological Education: Some Reflections That May Throw Some Light on the Quandries of the Divinity School" by Julian N. Hartt in Reflection, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 686)
  - University
    - "Swarthmore College", 1958 (Box 31, Folder 687)
    - "A Divinity School in a Modern University" by Wilfrid Cantrell Smith, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 688)
    - "Athens and Jerusalem Revisited" by Harry Smith, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 689)
    - "'Reason for Being' at Union and Yale" by James E. Dittes and Charles W. Powers in Christian Century, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 690)
    - "Change in the Corporations: Needed: A New Consensus" by George C. Lodge in Harvard Today, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 691)
    - "Theological Studies in a University Seminary" by George Lindbeck, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 692)
    - "The Underwood Study Revisited" by Harry E. Smith in Reflection, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 693)
    - "What is Innovation Really?" by Leon Botstein in Change, v.4 n.3, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 694)
    - "A Composite from the Most Recent Financial Reports of the Universities of California at Berkeley, Chicago, Columbia, Harvard, Notre Dame, Vanderbilt and Yale", 1973 (Box 31, Folder 695)
    - "An Introduction to the Study of Church History" by H. M. Goodpasture, J. H. Smylie, and Charles Davidson, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 696)
    - "Union Seminary", 1973 (Box 31, Folder 697)
    - "The Coming Shakeout in Higher Education" in Forbes, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 698)
    - "Consultation on University-Related Theological Education", 1974 (Box 31, Folder 699)
    - "Consultation on University-Related Theological Education", 1974 (Box 31, Folder 700)
    - "Description of a Projected 'Report on Theological Education Within the University'" by George Lindbeck, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 701)
    - "Description of a Projected 'Report on Theological Education Within the University'" by George Lindbeck, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 702)
    - "The Divinity School Fields and Programs at Mid-Decade" in Criterion: A Publication of the Divinity School of the University of Chicago, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 703)
    - "A Forum on the Study of Religion in the University" by Walter H. Capps in Journal of the American Academy of Religion, v. XLII, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 704)